Ayomide Akintimehin

Front end Engineer

I am a front end engineer with over 12 months of professional experience. My strongest asset is my very positive mentality and great zeal to improve rapidly and get things done whatsoever which has reflected so much with my experience with Vanilla JS, Vue.js, React.js, Ionic-Vue in such a short time.

I strongly believe that the mind is our greatest tool and with the right mindset, anything is achievable so I am not shy of taking on a new challenge or adopting a new technology. I am very open to working remotely, as I have done successfully over the last year, and also very willing to relocate.

10 Ayorinde street, Ogba Lagos, Nigeria (234) 814-011-3415 ayoakinti@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Gricd Integrated Services, Nigeria —Frontend Engineer Intern

MAR 2020 - SEP 2020

"Happy birthday to the ever zealous @Ayomide Akintimehin" - a comment from the CEO after working with me for just 2 months

- I rebuilt the entire web application of the company using the Vue.js framework which was formerly written with PHP
- Optimized my code sufficiently, to ensure a response time of less than 3 seconds.

Gricd Integrated Services, Nigeria — Frontend Engineer

SEP 2020 - PRESENT

"You deserved it bro; your zeal and drive is an inspiration to me" - another comment from the <u>CEO</u> when I thanked him for the opportunities granted me so far in the company

After a very remarkable internship, I was offered a full time role as the frontend engineer of the company.

- Maintenance of company's web application
- Implementation of additional features and user experience improvements across the application

EDUCATION

University of Lagos, Nigeria — B.Sc Mechanical Engineering

NOV 2014 - OCT 2018

GPA - 4.28/5

SKILLS

I am an excellent communicator of my ideas.

I work greatly and seamlessly with a team.

PROJECTS

My Portfolio
Gricd Web Application
Github Link
LinkedIn Profile

HONOURS & AWARDS

Enyata Project Build-up-Was selected as one of the top 50 young techies from over 5,000 applicants.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Completed 2 Courses by Coursera on Data Structures and Algorithms

- Algorithmic Toolbox
- Data Structures